dancarlin.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy

Orator LLC and dancarlin.com

## **PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last modified: August 1, 2016**

  1. **Introduction.** Orator LLC and dancarlin.com (“Company” or “We”) and its affiliates respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the Website located at [dancarlin.com](https://www.dancarlin.com/) (this “Site”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.
  2. **Information Collected.** This policy applies to information we collect: 
    * On this Site;
    * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Site; and
    * When you interact with our shopping cart system, affiliates, social media as well as any links to this policy.
  3. **Excluded Information.** This policy does not apply to information collected by: 
    * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other Site operated by Company or any third party; or
    * Any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on this Site.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Site. By accessing or using this Site, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

  4. **Children Under the Age of 13.** Our Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age (It is intended for users that are 18 years of age or older). No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to this Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Site or on or through any of its features/register on this Site, make any purchases through this Site, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#472f222b37072326292426352b2e296924282a)

  5. **Information We Collect About You.** We may collect several types of information from and about users of our Site, including information: 
    * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or other details to help with your experience (“personal information”);
    * that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as current or past tenancies, property ownership or management and other related information; and/or
    * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Site and usage details.
  6. **How We Collect Information.** We collect information from you in the following ways: 
    * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
    * Automatically as you navigate through this Site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.
    * From third parties, for example, our business payment and Podcast
  7. **Information You Provide to Us.**
    * The information we collect on or through our Site may include: 
      * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Site.
      * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
      * Your responses to surveys or questions that we might ask you to complete for research including customer service purposes.
      * Details of transactions you carry out through our Site and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Site.
      * Your search queries on this Site.
    * You also may provide information to be viewable by (hereinafter, “posted”) or transmitted to other approved members of this Site or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to your personal information if requested, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of this Site with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.
  8. **Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.**
    * As you navigate through and interact with our Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including: 
      * Details of your visits to our Site, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on this Site.
      * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.
    * We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. It’s also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking.

  * The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to: 
    * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
    * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Site according to your individual interests.
    * Speed up your searches.
    * Recognize you when you return to our Site.
  * The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include: 
    * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Site.
    * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Site may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Site. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.
    * Web Beacons. Pages of this Site and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related Site statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain Site content and verifying system and server integrity).

  9. **Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.**
    * Some content or applications, including advertisements, on this Site are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Site. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different Sites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.
    * We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
  10. **How We Use Your Information.**
    * We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information: 
      * To restrict access to your account and personal information.
      * To present our Site and its contents to you.
      * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
      * To fulfill any other purpose or product for which you provide it.
      * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
      * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
      * To notify you about changes to our Site or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
      * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Site.
      * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
      * For any other purpose with your consent.
    * We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please notify us by sending an email stating your request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
    * We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.
  11. **Disclosure of Your Information.**
    * We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy: 
      * To our subsidiaries and affiliates or third party fulfillment services.
      * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
      * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
      * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
      * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
      * With your consent.
    * We may also disclose your personal information: 
      * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
      * To enforce or apply our terms of use (www.dancarlin.com) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
      * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Insight Data Services, Inc., our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  12. **Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.**
    * We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 
      * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s [Site](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
      * Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
      * Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your email address or contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to www.dancarlin.com If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions.

  * We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s Site.

  13. **Accessing and Correcting Your Information**
    * You can review and change your personal information by logging into this Site and visiting this privacy policy.
    * You may also send us an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.
    * If you delete your User Contributions from this Site, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Site users. Proper access and use of information provided on this Site, including User Contributions, is governed by our privacy policy.
  14. **Data Security**
    * We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions and all collected data is encrypted using SSL technology.
    * The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a username and password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this username and password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.
    * Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on this Site.
  15. **Changes to Our Privacy Policy.** It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on this Site’s home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Site and this privacy policy to check for any changes.
  16. **Contact Information.** To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

**Dan Carlin                 **

1430 Willamette St. #22

Eugene, OR 97401

[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
